Irving P. Krick papers, 1921-1996
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Weather Modification Project
  - Correspondence: Tri-Counties Rural Development Association, Montana (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Contract: Boyne Mountain Lodge, Michigan (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence: Boyne Mountain Lodge, Michigan (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Contracts: Dow Chemical Company, Midland Division, Michigan (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence: Dow Chemical Company, Midland Division, Michigan (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Coke fuel production study (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Client reports: Sherman Cooperative Grain Growers, Oregon (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Client reports: Crop Protection Incorporated, Oregon (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Client reports: Weather Modification Incorporated (Rob Brown), Texas (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Client reports: Dow Chemical Company, Texas (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Client reports: Provincial Government of Ontario, Canada (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Client reports: Freedom State Bank, Oklahoma (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Client reports: Arbuckle Weather Modification District, Oklahoma (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Client reports: Kiowa City Weather Modification Association, Oklahoma (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Client reports: Horse Heaven Water Development Corporation, Washington (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Client reports: Red Bluff Water Power Control District, Texas (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Client reports: Courtright Cattle Company Incorporated, Washington (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Client reports: Hitch AGRI-Business Incorporated, Oklahoma (1 of 2) (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Client reports: Hitch AGRI-Business Incorporated, Oklahoma (2 of 2) (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Client reports: Oklahoma State University (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Client reports: Ellis County Weather Incorporated (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Client reports: Harper County Weather Incorporated (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Interim Report for the Texas Trans Pecos Area, for Red Bluff Power Control District (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Interim Report for the Texas Trans Pecos Area, for Red Bluff Power Control District (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Precipitation data for Minnesota (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Precipitation data for Iowa (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Client reports: Beaver County Weather Incorporated, Oklahoma (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Client reports: Washita County Weather Modification Association, Oklahoma (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Client reports: Big Bend Water Development Corporation, Washington (1 of 2) (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Client reports: Big Bend Water Development Corporation, Washington (2 of 2) (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Client reports: Custer County Weather Association, Oklahoma (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Client reports: Oklahoma Water Resources Board (1 of 2) (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Client reports: Oklahoma Water Resources Board (2 of 2) (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Client reports: Gratiot County modification Limited, Michigan (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Foreign prospect: United Arab Emirates (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Foreign prospect: Turkey (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Foreign prospect: Tunisia (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Local prospect: Nevada (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Local prospect: Nebraska (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Local prospect: New York (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Foreign prospect: Saudi Arabia (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Local prospect: Oklahoma (1 of 2) (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Local prospect: Oklahoma (2 of 2) (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Local prospect: Oklahoma - articles (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Los Angeles lawsuit (1 of 3) (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Los Angeles lawsuit (2 of 3) (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Los Angeles lawsuit (3 of 3) (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Local prospect: Illinois (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Oklahoma lawsuit (1 of 2) (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Oklahoma lawsuit (2 of 2) (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Local prospect: Arkansas (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Local prospect: Upper Colorado River Commission, Colorado (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Local prospect: Arizona (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Local prospect: Alaska (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Local prospect: form letters (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Local prospect: Colorado River Basin (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Local prospect: Colorado (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence (1 of 2) (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence (2 of 2) (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Evaluation of Five Years of Operation of the Utah Weather Modification Operation (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Map: Wyoming highways (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Local prospect: Idaho (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Local prospect: New Mexico (1 of 2) (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Local prospect: New Mexico (2 of 2) (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Local prospect: New Jersey (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Local prospect: New Hampshire (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Local prospect: Washington, D.C., Department of the Interior, Bureau of Land Management (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Foreign prospect: Spain (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Foreign prospect: Belgium (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Foreign prospect: Alberta, Canada (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Foreign prospect: Canada (1 of 2) (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Foreign prospect: Canada (2 of 2) (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Local prospect: California (1 of 2) (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Local prospect: California (2 of 2) (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Local prospect: Rapid City Flood, South Dakota (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Court transcript: Dolores Sher vs. Southern California Gas Company, Deposition of Irving Krick (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Court transcript: Ellis Nourafchan vs. Phillip N. Gepner, Deposition of James Robert Stinson (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Court transcript: Ellis Nourafchan vs. Phillip N. Gepner, et al., Supplemental Points (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Foreign prospect: Venezuela (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Local prospect: Colorado (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Local prospect: Utah (1 of 2) (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Local prospect: Utah (2 of 2) (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - United States Navy (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Olympic Winter Games, Squaw Valley, CA (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Graphs: Alberta (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Paper: Alberta Hail Research, A Major Agricultural Disaster: J.T. Bishop (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Colorado State Board of Registration for Professional Engineers and Land Surveyers (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Foreign prospect: Saudi Arabia, National Geographic, Vol. 129, No. 1 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Foreign prospect: Australia, Bob Hawke's Australia - A Survey (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Numerical Simulation of Large Convective Clouds, Takao Takeda (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Climatological Data, Vol. XVI, No. 5, U.S. Department of Agriculture, Weather Bureau (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Study of the Length of Record Needed to Obtain Satisfactory Climatic Summaries, Army Air Force (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Upper Air Values of Temperature, Pressure, and Relative Humidity ovver the U.S. and Alaska (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Wind charts (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - NavAer, Ch. IV, paragraphs 452-453 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Climatological Data, U.S. Department of Agriculture, Weather Bureau (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Monthly Record, Meteorological Observations in Canada and Newfoundland (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Report of the Bonneville Power Administration, Cloud Seeding Operations - U.S. Department of the Interior (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Proposal for Colorado River Basin Pilot Project, Page Communications Engineers Inc. (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Proposal: An Opportunity Recognition and Cloud Seeding System for Operational Weather Modification Research, U.S. Department of the Interior (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Monthly Record, Meteorological Observations in Canada and Newfoundland (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Monthly Record, Meteorological Observations in Canada and Newfoundland (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Monthly Record, Meteorological Observations in Canada and Newfoundland (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Monthly Record, Meteorological Observations in Canada and Newfoundland (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Monthly Record, Meteorological Observations in Canada and Newfoundland (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Monthly Record, Meteorological Observations in Canada and Newfoundland (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Monthly Record, Meteorological Observations in Canada and Newfoundland (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Monthly Record, Meteorological Observations in Canada and Newfoundland (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Final Report on the 1975 Alberta Ground Generator Study, Part I: Newton C. Stone, et al. (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Record, Upper Colorado Basin Compact Commission (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Compendium of Meteorology, Edited by Thomas Malone (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Monthly Record, Meteorological Observations in Canada and Newfoundland (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Monthly Record, Meteorological Observations in Canada and Newfoundland (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Climatological Service Report, Colorado (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Climatological Service Report, Illinois (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Climatological Service Report, Iowa (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Climatological Service Report, Kansas (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Climatological Service Report, Louisiana (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Climatological Service Report, Michigan (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Climatological Service Report, Mississippi (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Climatological Service Report, New Mexico (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Climatological Service Report, New York (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Climatological Service Report, North Dakota (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Climatological Service Report, Pennsylvania (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Climatological Service Report, South Carolina (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Climatological Service Report, Tennessee (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Climatological Service Report, Utah (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - Climatological Service Report, Wisconsin (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Report on the Weather Modification Operations in Western and Central Minnesota for the Summer and Fall of 1976 (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - Monthly Record, Meteorological Observations in Canada (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - Climatological Data, West Virginia (Box 44, Folder 18)
  - Climatological Data, Washington (Box 44, Folder 19)
  - Climatological Data, Wisconsin (Box 44, Folder 20)
  - Climatological Data, Wyoming (Box 44, Folder 21)
  - Climatological Data, Virginia (Box 44, Folder 22)
  - Climatologicla Data, Utah (Box 44, Folder 23)
  - Climatological Data, Alaska (Box 44, Folder 24)
  - Climatological Data, National Summary (Box 44, Folder 25)
  - Climatological Data, Texas Annual Summary (Box 44, Folder 26)
  - Monthly Record, Meteorological Observations in Canada (Box 44, Folder 27)
  - Report of the Climatological Survey, Iowa (Box 44, Folder 28)
  - Report of the Climatological Survey, Districts 1-9 (Box 44, Folder 29)
  - Report of the Climatological Survey, Districts 1-10 (Box 44, Folder 30)
  - Report of the Climatological Survey, various states (Box 44, Folder 31)
  - Michigan Lawsuit: Correpsondence (1 of 3) (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Michigan Lawsuit: Correspondence (2 of 3) (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Michigan Lawsuit: Correspondence (3 of 3) (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Active client: Edwards Underground Water District (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Local prospect:San Angelo, TX (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Tracings (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Daily summaries (1 of 3) (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Daily summaries (2 of 3) (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Daily summaries (3 of 3) (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Daily summaries (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Daily summaries (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Daily summaries (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Daily summaries (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Daily summaries (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Daily summaries (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Daily summaries (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Daily summaries (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Daily summaries (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Daily summaries (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Daily summaries (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Daily summaries (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Daily summaries (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Daily summaries (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Daily summaries (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Daily summaries (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Daily summaries (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Precipitation data, Georgia (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Precipitation data, Louisiana (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Precipitation data, Maryland (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Precipitation data, Colorad (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Precipitation data, British Columbia (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Precipitation data, Montana (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Precipitation data, Michigan (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Precipitation normals, Oklahoma (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Client reports: Grand Mesa Water Users Incorporated, Colorado (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Client reports: International Paper Company, Louisiana (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Client reports: Grand Mesa Water Users Incorporated, Colorado (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Client reports: MacMillan, Bloedel, and Powell River Limited, British Columbia (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Client reports: Delaware Weather Modification Program, Delaware (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Client reports: Harvey's Peanut Company, Georgia (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Client reports: Grand Mesa Water Users Incorporated, Colorado (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Client reports: Diamond "A" Cattle Company, New Mexico (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Client reports: Operation Snowflake Incorporated, New Mexico (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Client reports: Morrow County Weather Research Association, Oregon (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Client reports: T.E. Mitchell and Son Incorporated, New Mexico (1 of 2) (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Client reports: T.E. Mitchell and Son Incorporated, New Mexico (2 of 2) (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Client reports: Big Stone Weather Incorporated, Minnesota (1 of 2) (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Client reports: Big Stone Weather Incorporated, Minnesota (2 of 2) (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Client reports: C.V. Griffin Groves Company, Florida (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Final report: Kiowa County Weather Modification Association (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Final report: Weather Modification Inc., Texas (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Final report: Weather Modification Inc., Texas (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Final report: Lawton, Oklahoma (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Final report: Comanche County Weather Modification Inc., Oklahoma (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Final report: Oklahoma Farm and Ranch Areas (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Final report: Harper County Weather Inc., Oklahoma (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Final report: Cotton County Services Inc., Oklahoma (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - Final report: Harper County Weather Inc., Oklahoma (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - Final report: Cotton County Services Inc., Oklahoma (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - Final report: Cotton County Services Inc., Oklahoma (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - Final report: Cotton County Services Inc., Oklahoma (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Final report: Cotton County Services Inc., Oklahoma (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Final report: Cotton County Services Inc., Oklahoma (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Final report: Cotton County Services Inc., Oklahoma (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Final report: Cotton County Services Inc., Oklahoma (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Final report: Washita County Weather Modification Association, Oklahoma (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Client reports: State of Oklahoma (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Client reports: National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Weather Modification in Alberta: Brochures (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - A Weather Engineering Proposal (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - The Krick Group Program (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - Final Operation Report on 1985 Ground Generator Assessment and Weather Modification Operation (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence: Jim Bishop (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - Foreign prospect: Spain (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - Client reports: Red Bluff Water Power Control District (Box 52, Folder 16)
  - Client reports: Alberta Research Council (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Client reports: Alberta Research Council (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Client reports: Alberta Research Council (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Active client: Northwestern Colorado Weather Improvement, Colorado (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Alberta Weather Modification Co-op Proposal, by Jim Bishop (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Client reports: Alberta Research Council (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Active client: Powell River Company Ltd, British Columbia (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Active client: San Juan Weather Improvement Association, Colorado (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - Active client: Northern Colorado Natural Resources Association (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - Active client: Springfield City Water Co., Missouri (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - Active client: Spain (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - Active client: Snowpack, Platte Valley Water Resource and Bill Farr Group, Colorado (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - Active client: Berthoud Pass Lodge, Colorado (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Active client: Georgia-Alabama Water Conservation Corp. (Box 53, Folder 16)
  - Active client: Iowa Weather Modification Corp. (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Active client: Big Horn Weather Development Corp. (Box 53, Folder 18)
  - Active client: More Rain Inc., Kentuky (Box 53, Folder 19)
  - Active client: Midland Empire Weather Modification Association, Missouri and Kansas (Box 53, Folder 20)
  - Active client: Georgia Weather Modification Corporation (Box 53, Folder 21)
  - Active client: T.M. Dines and Associates, Colorado (Box 53, Folder 22)
  - Active client: Water Resources Development Corporation, Colorado (Box 53, Folder 23)
  - Active client: Mill Iron Ranch, Texas (Box 53, Folder 24)
  - Active client: Penninsular Water Conservation Association, Florida (Box 53, Folder 25)
  - Active client: Citizens' Water Conservation Association, Florida (Box 53, Folder 26)
  - Active client: MacMillan, Bloedel and Powell River, British Columbia (Box 53, Folder 27)
  - Engineering report: Cloud seeding potentialities in Queensland, Australia (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Final report: Ellis County Weather Inc., Oklahoma (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Final report: Woodward County Cloudseeding Association, Oklahoma (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Final report: Red Bluff Water Power Control District, Texas (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Final report: Red Bluff Water Power Control District, Texas (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Active client: Kneehill Association, Alberta (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Active client: Southwestern Oklahoma (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Final report: Beaver County Weather Inc., Oklahoma (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Louis Scott's forecast, Florida (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - Final reports: Red Bluff Water Power Control District, Texas (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Final reports: Kittitas County, Washington (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Final report: Washington's Cattlemans Association (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - Final report: Ellis County Weather Inc., Oklahoma (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - Final report: Beaver CountyWeather Inc., Oklahoma (Box 54, Folder 16)
  - Monthly and final reports for the State of Oklahoma (1 of 2) (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Monthly and final reports for the State of Oklahoma (2 of 2) (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Material for Ruben Gabriel (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Alberta: Miscellaneous correspondence (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Final report: Alberta Research Council (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Active client: Alberta (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Active client: Kneehill Association, Alberta (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Precipitation data: Louisiana (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Precipitation data: Louisiana (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Precipitation data: Louisiana (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Active client: Rainer Development Corporation, Alberta (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Active client: Alberta Weather Modification Corporation (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Local prospect: Mississippi (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Local prospect: Texas (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Local prospect: Maryland (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Local prospect: Maine (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Local prospect: Iowa (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - Local prospect: Indiana (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - Local prospect: Montana (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - Local prospect: Louisiana (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - Local prospect: Minnesota (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Local prospect: Texas (1 of 2) (Box 57, Folder 15)
  - Local prospect: Texas (2 of 2) (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Local prospect: Washington, D.C., National Air Pollution, Environmental Protection Agency (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Local prospect: Washington, D.C., NASA (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Local prospect: Washington, D.C., Federal (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Local prospect: Wisconsin (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Local prospect: Wyoming (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Local prospect: Pennsylvania (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Local prospect: North Carolina (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Local prospect: Washington, D.C., Miscellaneous non-governmental (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - Local prospect: Washington, D.C., Senate hearings (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - Local prospect: Washington (1 of 2) (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - Local prospect: Washington (2 of 2) (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - Local prospect: Kentucky (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - Foreign prospect: South Africa (1 of 2) (Box 58, Folder 14)
  - Foreign prospect: South Africa (2 of 2) (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Foreign prospect: Philippine Islands (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Foreign prospect: Poland (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Client reports: Alberta Research Council (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Foreign prospect: Saudi Arabia (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Local prospect: Missouri (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Locla prospect: Washington D.C., Department of the Interior (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Local prospect: California, Palm Springs smog (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - Newspaper clipipngs: Oklahoma (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Local prospect: South Carolina (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Local prospect: California, Los Angeles smog (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Local prospect: California, Los Angeles smog (1 of 3) (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Local prospect: California, Los Angeles smog (2 of 3) (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Local prospect: California, Los Angeles smog (3 of 3) (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Local prospect: Colorado (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Local prospect: California, Riverside smog (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Local prospect: California, Palm Springs, blow sand (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Local prospect: California, Pacific Gas and Electric Company (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - Foreign prospect: Saudi Arabia (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - Foreign prospect: Brazil (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Local prospect: Colorado (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Foreign prospect: Australia (1 of 2) (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Foreign prospect: Australia (2 of 2) (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Foreign prospect: Saudi Arabia (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Foreign prospect: Australia (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Foreign prospect: Australia (1 of 2) (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Foreign prospect: Australia (2 of 2) (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - Foreign prospect: Saudi Arabia (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Tracings (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Tracings (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Tracings (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Tracings (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Tracings (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Tracings (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Tracings (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Tracings (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Tracings (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Tracings (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Tracings (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Tracings (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Tracings (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Tracings (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Tracings (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Tracings (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Daily log of Weather Modification Operations (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Daily log of Weather Modification Operations (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Bibliography of Weather Modification Research using IPK facilities (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Weather maps (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Daily log (1 of 2) (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Daily log (2 of 2) (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Active client: North Dakota Weather Modification Board (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Active client: North Dakota Weather Modification Board (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - Active client: North Dakota Weather Modification Board (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Local prospect: North Dakota (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - Weather maps: Eastern U.S. (1 of 5) (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - Weather maps: Eastern U.S. (2 of 5) (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - Weather maps: Eastern U.S. (3 of 5) (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Weather mpas: Eastern U.S. (4 of 5) (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Weather maps: Eastern U.S. (5 of 5) (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Foreign prospect: Thailand (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Foreign prospect: Switzerland (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Foreign prospect: Portugal (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Active client: Oklahoma (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Active client: Oklahoma (Box 66, Folder 11)